

Hudson Kennedy
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Email:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Phone (21) 9 6960-9121



ABOUT ME

I had contact with the technology area about 10 years ago, working with VB.net and HTML, during the journey I took some courses, where in 2018 I started my Technologist in management processes and in return I went back to the technology area, to work with Javascript, specifically in Frontend, where I have studied and taken several courses, graduated in Process Management, with an emphasis on Process Management and Optimization, and I always wanted to acquire more knowledge and evolve professionally. In 2021 I started my MBA in Software Engineering, where I learned many new things and continue to evolve every day. I will continue to improve myself daily as a Fullstack Developer and Software Engineer, seeking to acquire more experience and knowledge!



EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer

August 2022 - at moment

VILT Brazil Information Systems

Cast Group

Working directly with the

Fullstack Consulting, working with Java in Backend and Angular/React in Frontend, using Platform programs Adobe Experience Manager(AEM), providing services for several clients such as Porto, CVC and etc.

Bosch customer, in the directives and maintenance/refactoring negotiations

code using Angular and Typescript.

Full Technical Consultant

January 2022 - April 2022

E-commerce Analyst / Front-end Developer

February 2019 - June 2021

DT3 Group

Invoice issuance, marketplaces, website development in React.JS, image optimization and responsible for ERP Bling integration.

Freelancers/Personal Works

February 2012 - at moment

99Freelas/Capitona Rio/ETERJ

I took an industrial IT course at ETERJ, and freelance work, using Angular Js, VB.net, HTML, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap, Sass.



ACADEMIC EDUCATION

Harvard University

2023

Post Graduate

Science Computer

Single College of MG

2021 - 2022

MBA

Software Engineering

Estácio de Sá College

2018 - 2020

Technologist

Management processes



Hudson Kennedy SOFTWARE ENGINEER FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Email:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

Phone (21) 9 6960-9121



HTML/CSS/Javascript/Jquery
Angular/React/VueJs/NodeJs/Svelte
Git/Github/NPM/YARN/
Wordpress/Shopify/Bling
APIs/Markdown/Material Design
Bootstrap/Typescript/
Figma/Photoshop/Material UI
Less/Sass/TailwindCss/
Google Analytics/Google Ads
JAVA/PHP/Laravel/AWS/Firebase
Docker/Webpack/Springboot
C#/Python/Swagger/GraphQL
PostgreSQL/Vuetify/Pinia

P

EXTRACURRICULAR COURSES

DIO - Components, Methods and Lifecycle with Vue.js - 2022

DIO - Component Properties and Directives with Vue.js - 2022

DIO - Bootcamp Eduzz - Fullstack Developer - 2022

DIO - Working with SPA Pages with Angular - 2022

DIO - Working with Components in React - 2022

DIO - Component architecture and front-end complexity - 2022

Adobe Professional – AEM Sites Business Practitioner - 2022

Adobe Professional – AEM Front-End Developer - 2022

Let's Code Course (Santander) - Dev Fullstack - 2021

MERN Stack Course (MongoDB, Express, React & NodeJS -

FaculdadeIV2 - 2021

Initial Vuejs Course - Vuejs Brazil - 2021

Basic to Advanced Javascript & Typescript Course (HTML/CSS/

NodeJs/React/MySQL/PostgreSQL/MariaDB/ - Udemy - 2020



LANGUAGES

Spanish - Basic French - Basic Italian - Basic English - Advanced



ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Excel/Word /Power Point
Teams/Outlook/Skype
System Configurations
Windows
Computer Domain
Typing
Document Archiving
Internet in general
Google Chrome/Mozilla/Opera